forex.ee 2017-07-05

# Privacy Policy

 Privacy Policy
                            NetStock Ltd
Cedar Hill Crest, Villa, Kingstown, St. Vincent and the Grenadines

        PERSONAL INFORMATION
NetStock Ltd (hereinafter referred to as “the Company” or “we”) collects information required to open
an account, to transact business effectively and to safeguard Customers (hereinafter referred to as
“you”) assets and privacy. To do this, we gather information to help us assess your needs and
preferences.
The information we collect directly from you includes information required to communicate with you,
including: your name, address, birth date, occupation, assets and income, telephone number, e-mail
address.
We also collect birth date and your location information
     -  transaction information: Information about your transactions with us and with our affiliates as
        well as information about our communications with you. Examples include your account
        balances, trading activity, your inquiries, and our responses;
     -  verification information: Information necessary to verify your identity, such as a passport or
        driver's license. Examples also include background information about you we receive from
        public records or from other entities not affiliated with the Company.
We use personal information only as appropriate to provide you quality service and security. For
example, we may use the information collected from you to verify your identity and contact
information. We may also use this information to establish and set up your trading account, issue an
account number and a secure password, maintain your account activity, and contact you with account
information. This information helps us improve our services to you, inform you about additional
products, services or promotions that may be of interest to you.
        OUR AFFILIATES AND PARTNERS
We may share information with affiliates if the information is required to provide the product or
service you have requested or to provide you the opportunity to participate in the products or services
our affiliates offer. Our affiliates may include companies controlled or owned by us as well as
companies that have an ownership interest in our company. We may also forge partnerships and
alliances, which may include joint marketing agreements, with other companies who offer high-quality
products and services that might be of value to our Customers. In order to ensure that these products
and services meet your needs and are delivered in a manner that is useful and relevant, we may share
some information with partners, affiliates and alliances. This allows them to better understand the
offers that are most relevant and useful. The use of your personal information is limited to the
purposes identified in our relationship with the partner or affiliate. The information we share with
                                                   NetStock Ltd
                       Cedar Hill Crest, Villa, Kingstown, St. Vincent and the Grenadines
                                                        2

affiliates may include any of the information described above, such as your name, address, trading and
account information.
         NON-AFFILIATED THIRD PARTIES
We do not sell, license, lease or otherwise disclose your personal information to any third party for
any reason, except as described below.
We may also disclose your information as necessary to credit reporting or collection agencies, or when
necessary to protect our rights or property.
To help us improve our services to you, we may engage another business to help us to carry out
certain internal functions such as account processing, fulfillment, Customer service, Customer
satisfaction surveys or other data collection activities relevant to our business, legal or accounting
services. We may also provide a party with Customer information from our database to help us to
analyze and identify Customer needs and notify Customers of product and service offerings. Use of the
information shared is strictly limited to the performance of the task we request and for no other
purpose. All third parties with which we share personal information are required to protect personal
information in a manner similar to the way we protect personal information.
         REGULATORY DISCLOSURE
Under limited circumstances, the Company may disclose your personal information to third parties as
permitted by, or to comply with, applicable laws and regulations. For example, we may disclose
personal information to cooperate with regulatory authorities and law enforcement agencies to
comply with subpoenas or other official requests, and as necessary to protect our rights or property.
Except as described in this Privacy Policy, we will not use your personal information for any other
purpose, unless we describe how such information will be used at the time you disclose it to us or we
obtain your permission.
         RESTRICTION OF RESPONSIBILITY
                                                   NetStock Ltd
                       Cedar Hill Crest, Villa, Kingstown, St. Vincent and the Grenadines
                                                        3

If at any time you choose to purchase a product or service offered by another company, any personal
information you share with that company will no longer be controlled under our Privacy Policy. We
are not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of sites we link to and have no control of the
use or protection of information provided by you or collected by those sites. Whenever you elect to
link to a co-branded Web site or to a linked Web site, you may be asked to provide registration or
other information. Please note that the information you are providing is going to a third party, and you
should familiarize yourself with the privacy policy provided by that third party.
         OPTING OUT OF DISCLOSURES OF NON-PUBLIC PERSONAL
         INFORMATION
You are not required to supply any of the personal information that we may request; however, failure
to do so may result in our being unable to open or maintain your account or to provide services to you.
While we make every effort to ensure that all information we hold about you is accurate, complete, and
up to date, you can help us considerably in this regard by promptly notifying us if there are any
changes to your personal information. You may direct us not to disclose non-public personal
information to certain non-affiliated third parties. To opt out of sharing non-public personal
information with non-affiliated third parties, please contact a Customer service representative
support@forexee.com . An opt out election made by one account owner of a joint account is applicable
to all account owners of the joint account. An opt-out election must be made for each separate account
you hold with us.
         USE OF COOKIES
We use cookies to assist us in securing your trading activities and to enhance the performance of our
Web site. (Cookies are small text files sent from the Web server to your computer.) Cookies used by us
do not contain any personal information nor do they contain account or password information. They
merely allow the site to recognize that a page request comes from someone who has already logged
on.
We may share Web site usage information about visitors to the Web site with reputable advertising
companies for targeting our Internet banner advertisements on this site and other sites. For this
purpose, pixel tags (also called clear gifs or web beacons) may be used to note the pages you've visited.
The information collected by the advertising company through the use of these pixel tags is not
personally identifiable.
                                                   NetStock Ltd
                       Cedar Hill Crest, Villa, Kingstown, St. Vincent and the Grenadines
                                                        4

To administer and improve our Web site, we may use a third party to track and analyze usage and
statistical volume information, including page requests, form requests, and click paths. The third party
may use cookies to track behavior and may set cookies on behalf of us. These cookies do not contain
any personally identifiable information.
         COMMUNICATIONS
Unless otherwise indicated for a particular service, any communications or material of any kind that
you e-mail or otherwise transmit through the services, including information, data, questions,
comments or suggestions will be treated as non-proprietary and non-confidential.
By accepting the Customer Agreement you grant a license to us to use your Communications in any
way we think fit, either on the website or elsewhere, with no liability or obligation to you. We are free
to use any idea, concept, know-how or technique or information contained in your Communications
for any purpose including, but not limited to, developing and marketing products.
We are entitled, but not obligated, to review or retain your Communications.
We may monitor your Communications to evaluate the quality of service you receive, your compliance
with this Agreement, the security of the Web site, or for other reasons. You agree that such monitoring
activities will not entitle you to any cause of action or other right with respect to the manner in which
we monitor your Communications. In no event we will be liable for any costs, damages, expenses or
any other liabilities incurred by you as a result of our monitoring activities.
         CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy. In the event we materially change this Privacy
Policy, the revised Privacy Policy will promptly be posted to the websites and we will post a notice on
our websites informing you of such changes. You agree to accept posting of a revised Privacy Policy
electronically on the website as actual notice to you. Any dispute over our Privacy Policy is subject to
this notice and our Customer Agreement. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this
policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we
disclose it. If you have any questions that this statement does not address, please contact a Customer
Services representative.
                                                    NetStock Ltd
                        Cedar Hill Crest, Villa, Kingstown, St. Vincent and the Grenadines
                                                         5
